Please ask Master Fang Qingcheng to come out and speak.
I am Fang Zhuozhuo, paying my respects to Madam.
Paying respects to all the noble ladies.
You two sisters
are really interesting.
Substituting for marriage isn't enough;
you also substitute for the competition.
My cousin hasn't returned yet.
I really couldn't bear to see
Yanzhi Pavilion's years of hard work go to waste.
So I specifically took this opportunity to display the Flying Phoenix in Flames.
Every brushstroke on this
was developed by my cousin
and the sisters in the pavilion together.
Since all the ladies agree on its quality,
I hope Madam will make a fair decision
and grant Yanzhi Pavilion the honor it deserves.
Come here.
Nanny Chang.
I am here.
Move this Nine-Phoenix Candlestick over there.
I want to see
if this Flying Phoenix in Flames
is worthy of the title of champion.
Yes.
Someone, come.
Behave!
No!
Stop!
It hurts!
Let me go!
What does this have to do with her?
It's truly exquisite.
Bring it closer to me.
No!
Just now, Madam
seemed to appreciate this Flying Phoenix in Flames very much.
It's me being blind.
How can such vulgar makeup
match Madam's natural beauty?
It is truly difficult to be
the champion of the Makeup Selection Ceremony.
Even gold and iron
will melt in a raging fire.
Madam's action
not only damages the official reputation of the ceremony,
but also chills the hearts of all the makeup artists in Kuizhou.
How dare you!
A repudiated thin slave
dares to argue with me?
From the moment you stepped into the gates of this Governor's Mansion,
it was a capital offense.
No matter how exquisite
your makeup is,
a thin woman's makeup
is inherently lowly.
Guards!
Drag this thin slave who violated the Crime Appearance Doctrine away
and lock her
in the death cell.
The copper rouge box you mentioned,
where is it now?
Madam,
you're finally willing to see me.
Speak.
It's with Chu Shengyi.
Madam is so smart;
naturally, you can guess everything.
Chu Shengyi even tried to cancel
the engagement with the Cheng family for you.
And you have the heart to betray him.
Deliberately luring me here,
what exactly do you want to do?
I only ask Madam
to acknowledge Yanzhi Pavilion's
position as the champion.
For a mere Yanzhi Pavilion,
you're willing to betray your beloved?
My cousin has been very kind to me.
I hope Madam will grant this.
Fang
Qingcheng.
Madam,
you actually have Qionghua Rouge too.
I should have known
I'd been played by you for so long.
I can make it so that even after the rouge's poison flares up,
you can maintain your plump appearance.
For this rouge,
there are only two ways
to revert the effects.
One is to wipe it off in time,
and the other is for the poison to fade away.
But if the poison penetrates too deeply for too long,
the duration will become
shorter and shorter.
For me right now,
it's 12 hours.
Madam, you've been using it
longer than I have.
I'm afraid
it's less than 8 hours now.
If this rouge is not reapplied after the poison flares up,
you will definitely revert to your original appearance,
which is quite troublesome.
So over the years,
I've been looking for a formula
to extend the duration of
this transforming rouge,
and I've gained quite some insights.
With just a few more tries,
I will definitely be able
to make a Qionghua Rouge
that transforms you permanently.
Really?
My life
is already in your hands, Madam.
Madam,
why not trust me this once?
If it really works,
I
will spare your miserable life.
Three days from now is the final of the Makeup Selection Ceremony.
I will participate in the competition as Qingcheng then.
When the time is right,
I will reveal my true face in front of Lady Li.
Substituting in the competition after substituting in the marriage,
Lady Li will definitely be furious.
Since she needs to control me,
she definitely won't take your life immediately.
After I'm imprisoned,
I'll find a way to lure her to meet me.
Then I'll intentionally expose a flaw
to let her know I also have the Qionghua Rouge.
And then tell her
that I have a way to extend the duration of the transformation.
She will definitely take the bait.
Have you figured out a method?
I have an idea.
If I can control the poison when it flares up,
perhaps I can extend the transformation time.
That will be enough to fool Lady Li.
I have received Jiaojiao's letter from the Western Regions.
She said there is a type of grass
that always grows next to the Qionghua flower.
We might give it a try.
How sure are you?
Fifty-fifty.
But
it's worth a gamble.
Her real issue is with me.
You can
use the bronze box rouge as an excuse
to lure her out to meet you.
You want me to sell you out?
No.
It's too risky.
All these years, Zier has been searching
for circumstantial evidence of her murdering my mother.
Only by releasing the evidence from back then
will she reveal her flaws.
Don't worry.
Her tricks over the years,
I have long figured them out.
Chu Shengyi,
you must hold on.
My Lord.
This hairpin,
it was on your birthday back then
that I personally put it on you.
My Lord,
you still remember.
Having too good a memory
is not necessarily a good thing.
My Lord,
is something on your mind?
You know
the knot in my heart all these years.
I have decided to let Yi'er
succeed as the heir.
Aunt Zhao's past affairs,
do not mention them in front of him
ever again.
I understand.
As for the salt trade,
these days,
let Yi'er follow your brother
to learn more.
He is intelligent
and will surely be of great help.
Since you have spoken,
I will naturally obey.
You are Yi'er's mother.
As long as you treat him well,
what you want,
you will naturally get.
My Lord,
won't you stay for a meal?
The kitchen made your favorite pineapple cake.
Keep it for yourself.
What I want most
has always been only you, My Lord.
I didn't kill you,
I didn't.
I killed someone again.
Madam.
The Commander left
definitely because he is busy.
Madam, in his heart,
you are always unmatched.
Perhaps in the past.
But now,
he has his flawless good son.
What am I?
Not only does he bring Chu Shengyi to discuss political affairs,
even the salt trade,
he wants my brother to hand over.
He is trying to strip the Li family of all their wealth and power
to pave the way for his beloved.
Madam.
Even if Chu Shengyi
lives to be the heir,
he may not live
to be the Lord of Kui State.
Zhuozhuo.
She escaped.
Mother,
why are you here?
Your breathing is getting sluggish,
and your limbs feel like lead,
right?
You...
poisoned me.
The news of Fang Zhuozhuo being at Qiwu Courtyard,
find a way to leak it out,
and lure him to the private garden.
There is poison in the blood.
I taught you long ago
to be vigilant about everything.
But you,
after all these years,
have you ever truly listened to me?
Soul-Suppressing Talisman.
Wonderful, isn't it?
These people
will never be reincarnated for eternity.
Even their souls
will be trapped here to suffer,
including
your mother.
It really is with you.
The makeup artist from Yanzhi Pavilion delivered the materials.
Have the items been checked?
Everything has been checked.
Why is this here?
This item once grew beside Qionghua.
It might be worth a try.
Madam.
An urgent dispatch from Anzhou.
The edict granting the concubine title has crossed Qingjiang.
After all these years,
it's finally my turn.
Chu Shengyi is dead.
If that lowly slave
can really make
the Qionghua rouge that brings permanent transformation,
then in the Master's eyes
and heart,
there will only ever be me.